(Sheldon:)Oh, boy.
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I can't comment without violating our
agreement that I not criticize your work.
- Then what was "Oh, boy"?
- Great restraint on my part.
(Leonard:)There's nothing wrong
with the science here.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps you mean a different thing
than I do when you say "science."
(Leonard(making a change):)Okay, how's that?
(Sheldon:)You actually had it right
in the first place.
(Sheldon:)Once again, you've fallen
for one of my classic pranks.
Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)Well, now, here's a peculiar e-mail.
(Sheldon:)The president of the university wants me
to meet him at his office at 8 a.m.
(Howard:)- Why?
- Doesn't say. Must be an emergency.
Everyone at the university knows
I eat breakfast at 8...
...and move my bowels at 8:20.
(Leonard:)Yes, how did we live before Twitter?
(Leonard:)I guess you'll find out what it is
in the morning.
(Sheldon:)That's 14 hours away.
(Sheldon:)For the next 840 minutes, I'm effectively
one of Heisenberg's particles.
I know where I am or how fast I'm going,
but I can't know both.
(Sheldon:)Yet how am I supposed to carry on...
(Sheldon:)...with this huge annoying thing
hovering over my head?
(Leonard:)Yeah, I know the feeling.